Prepare yourself!
Lightning Strike!
It's over!
The winner is Ariane Algren.
Sir?
Master?
Abbie?
Ray!
And who are these people with you?
So you've noticed.
Let me first tell you about the Hail family.
The Hail family?
Their bloodline has been responsible
for the kingdom's intelligence agency.
The dedicated maid for your beautiful master
is actually one of the kingdom's
best intelligence agents.
Miss Carla is an intelligence agent?
I can't believe you called
yourself beautiful, Lydia!
Thank you for looking after
my little brother, Ray.
Your little brother?
That's me.
Our club leader is Carla's little brother?!
I am Lex Hail.
With that revealed, nice to meet you again.
L-Likewise.
Let's get to business.
The Grim Reapers have infiltrated
the Magic Chevalier.
Dumbpink...
Beh.
Their aim is to kidnap the daughters of
the top noble houses, or murder them.
That's where you come in.
I want you to be vigilant, as well.
Since they are targeting students,
the probability that you will
encounter them is high.
Understood.
I'm sorry about this.
Lex is in charge of student security.
If anything happens, he can help you.
I'm counting on you, Ray.
Don't let your guard down.
If push comes to shove,
you can use that, too.
Hey, Lydia!
Eek!
Understood!
The Aywell Empire.
The Grim Reapers.
You will not get in the way
of Amelia and the others.
I'll stake my name on it
as the Iceblade Sorcerer.
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 8
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Inspires the Rose
The match is over!
With that, the beautiful
goddess Rebecca Bradley,
a third-year student of the
Arnold Academy of Sorcery,
has just advanced to the final
round of the main bracket!
Last year's champion really
showed us what she can do!
She's so strong! So strong!
And so beautiful!
She's the ultimate magic sword fighter!
Lady Rebecca will probably
be champion again this year!
Actually, nothing else makes sense!
The next match will be
Arnold Academy of Sorcery's Lurio Fuchia
Rebecca really is amazing.
versus Mercross Academy of
Sorcery's Lucas Forst!
She is.
Ray?
What's wrong?
Well you see... Amelia is...
Did something happen to her?
She won't come out of her room.
She says it's fatigue from yesterday, but...
Her voice sounds like she's suffering...
She won't tell us anything...
We're worried about her.
I see...
Ray.
Match over!
The match is over!
And what an unbelievable record!
The winner is Lucas Forst!
The match only took two seconds!
This is a record-breaking time
here at the Magic Chevalier!
An incredible dark horse
has just revealed himself!
T-Two seconds?!
Lucas Forst...
He's a second-year from Mercross.
There're some crazy people out there.
That's the spirit.
You're amazing!
Father, Tiana.
Here.
Thank you, Tiana.
We'll have to fix that again.
I'm so sorry, father.
Don't worry about it!
I'm looking forward to
tomorrow's competition.
I will definitely win.
Why don't you go?
Huh?
Elisa. Claris.
Ray.
Please help Amelia.
You're the only one who can help her now.
Yes.
I'll go tell her what I'm thinking.
Amelia!
It's me, Ray White!
You don't have to come out. Just listen.
I was... afraid.
Afraid to step into your heart.
I worried that if I got
too close to your heart,
I might accidentally break it.
I kept asking myself if my
decision had been the right one.
So I kept running away
from really facing you.
Amelia, I want you to tell me.
I want to know your heart!
Your heart...
I want to touch it.
Come in.
I really am hopeless.
You see, all I've done this whole time
is play-act everyone's
expectation of Amelia Rose.
Without any prompting, I imagined
everyone else's image of me,
and played the part.
All to become a me that's worthy
of being House Rose's eldest.
And I tried, and tried,
and tried, and tried,
and got this far.
But compared to everything
you've been through,
it's a big pile of nothing, isn't it?
There's no point in comparing
people's pasts, or their suffering.
However, it's certain that you've been
trying hard, despite all the suffering.
Isn't that true?
Yes. You're right.
For so long...
I've been hurting for so long...
I've suffered.
I've always wondered why I kept
on living when it hurt so badly.
Then I met everyone! I met you!
I thought that I could
actually attain something!
If I won this competition,
I could finally be someone.
That's what I was thinking, and yet...
I can't beat Ariane.
No matter how much time passes,
I'll never be anything but a bird in a cage.
Why?!
Why am I alive?!
I pretend, play the role of "me",
trying to materialize the
ideal version of myself,
but I still can't catch up to her!
Does this kind of life
even have any meaning?
Tell me, Ray!
Why am I alive?
Amelia, being alive has no meaning in itself.
There is no meaning to our existence.
But still!
But we, us humans, we can
find a reason to live!
You can create your own
reason for being alive.
Create... a reason?
Crying, laughing,
sorrows and joy,
sharing all that with your friends
and supporting each other in life.
Won't that do as your reason to live?
I want to keep living, next to you.
Really?
You don't mind having me around,
even when I'm weak like this?
I don't.
That is the real Amelia Rose, isn't it?
Now, then...
Amelia?
It's okay, Amelia.
I believe in you.
I know you can win.
Good night, Amelia.
Today we will be conducting
the final match for the rookie
bracket of the Magic Chevalier!
The contestants crossing blades will
be Ariane Algren and Amelia Rose!
Interestingly, this will be a match between
daughters of the great three noble houses!
Which of the two will be victorious?
The arena is fired up before
the match has even begun!
I'm sorry I'm late.
Ray.
Ray, where is Amelia?
She's fine now.
Really?
You did it, Ray!
Only because you had my back.
No, you're the one who did it.
Where's Claris?
She said she had to do some
organizational staff work.
I think she should be back soon.
I see. I'll have to thank her later, too.
I'm really glad it all worked out, though.
I was worried about whether Amelia
would be able to get some proper sleep.
You don't have to worry about that.
Huh?
I spent the whole night with her.
What?!
All... night?
Yes. She got plenty of sleep.
So you were there until morning?!
Yes?
Anyway, I'll go give Amelia her rose now.
I can't believe Ray would climb the
steps to adulthood so casually...
I don't think that happened, Evi.
Huh?
It's the same as always!
I mean, we're talking about Ray here!
Jeez, he always shocks me!
What?
I can't believe the organization
work took until now!
I'm not going to make it to Amelia's match!
It's almost time.
Yes.
You're fine now.
Ray, so... Well...
Could I... Could I get another hug?
Of course.
I'll get going, then.
Right.
If anyone can win, it's you, Amelia.
Yes.
My apologies, Sera.
Huh?
Something urgent has come up.
Now? But the match is about to start.
I really do apologize.
I'm counting on you.
Hey, wait up!
Sir.
Claris Cleveland, the daughter
of a high noble family,
has gone missing alongside
eight other noble students.
I will head below.
Below?
I feel something ominous from there.
I see.
Then I will check in with Lydia and
the others first before joining you.
Understood.
Caro caro!
Sorry I kept you waiting!
Miss Carol, where were you?
On. A. Date.
And we are back!
Youch, so cold!
We will now commence the final
match of the rookie bracket!
It's finally time, Amelia.
Indeed.
I will be winning this.
No, I will.
Then, let's settle this!
Let's!
And the match has begun!
It looks like competitor Algren
has thrown her sword away!
Ogre!
Why don't we begin at full power?
That's...
...the same move she used to defeat Albert.
An absurd display of speed!
What kind of sorcery is that?
That is one of her original spells.
It's a bit amazing that she has specialized
so much on the physical aspect.
I'm not done yet, Amelia!
Sister!
This... Is it really...?
I will...
never lose!
Claris!
Are you all right?
A huge stag beetle!
Claris, are you hurt?
H-Huh?
How did I get here?
What is this?
It's a wide-area interference spell.
They've begun.
Wide-area interference?
That's right.
This area is now shut off
from the outside world.
They must be the Grim Reapers.
Who are these guys?!
Claris, I'm sorry.
Huh? What!
Wait, Ray. Ray!
Don't speak for a while.
M-M-My skirt!
Chronos Lock, release!
No!
Icicle Blades!
Huh, what?!
This can't be happening...
No!
Claris, you're going to
bite your own tongue off!
But... but!
Now what?
Ray?
It's fine.
What on earth just happened?
Huh?
Anti-Material Field.
Oh, Ray.
You're not getting away!
Diamond Dust!
Wow!
It's like a world of ice.
Ray, is it over?
It is. I didn't kill them.
I see.
You can leave the rest of this to us.
Isn't there someone waiting for you?
Thank you.
Hey!
Put me down first!
The final match of the rookie
bracket, Algren vs Rose.
Neither contestant is backing down!
Both of them continue to trade blows!
I will be using the ace up my sleeve!
Ogre Scintilla!
Player Algren is sparking
to an unprecedented degree!
Father...
She's unleashed all of her bzz bzz!
Ariane!
Player Algren has gotten even shinier!
So this is the true form of
Ariane's original spell.
Unbelievable. She could get even stronger?!
Here I come!
You're too slow.
Explosions are nothing!
If they can't hit me!
R-Rose is down!
Is this going to be the end?!
It's over, Amelia.
Oh, I see.
I'm going to lose.
I really don't want to lose,
but my body won't move.
Amelia!
Amelia.
I want to keep living, next to you.
Amelia!
Get up!
Prima materia encoding
material code decoding
material code processing
αἰτία hū́lē eîdos
efficient télos embodiment
Causality.
What is this?
This is...
Ariane, you can no longer reach me.
Amelia...
Butterfly Effect.
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
~ Next Episode Preview ~
This is the preview of the next episode
of The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World!
Crimson butterflies dance, azure
lightning surges, and the battle rages on.
The two souls that parted ways that day
relentlessly speak through their fists.
"The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest
Sorcerer Releases the Binds".
Episode 9
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Releases the Binds
This has been Amelia Rose.